Junun is a music, documentary film directed by Paul Thomas Anderson.
A documentary capturing the creation of the album Junun
inside Rajasthan’s 15th-century Mehrangarh Fort.
Paul Thomas Anderson follows Jonny Greenwood, Shye Ben Tzur, Nigel Godrich, and the Rajasthan
Express as they record a cross-cultural fusion of Indian, Israeli, and Western music.
Self - Guitar, Flute, Vocals, Composer, played by Shye Ben Tzur.
Self - Dholak, played by Ehtisham Khan Ajmeri.
Self - Qawwali Chorus, played by Gufran Ali.
Self - Qawwali Chorus, played by Shazib Ali.
Self - Horns, played by Sabir Bamami.
Self - Trumpet, played by Aamir Bhiyani.
Junun is a 2015 documentary film directed by Paul Thomas Anderson.
It documents the making of the album Junun in Mehrangarh Fort in Rajasthan, India, by the Israeli composer Shye Ben Tzur, the English composer
and Radiohead guitarist Jonny Greenwood, the Indian ensemble the Rajasthan Express, and the Radiohead producer Nigel Godrich.
Junun premièred at the 2015 New York Film Festival and was released on the MUBI film
streaming service on October 9, 2015 and on iTunes on November 20, 2015.
It received critical acclaim.